IBT0059
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- From Microfilming Process, 1946-1986; Series 1; 28.5 Linear Feet
  - Microfilm 2200-2235, 1972-1975 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Microfilm 2236-2251, 1971-1974 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Microfilm 2252-2254, 1972-1975 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Microfilm 2255-2258, 1972-1975 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Microfilm 2259-2269, 1971-1974 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Microfilm 2270-2290, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Microfilm 2291-2299, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Microfilm 2300-2322, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Microfilm 2323-2344, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Microfilm 2345-2353, 1969-1971 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Microfilm 447, 1959-1964 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Microfilm 449, 1957-1963 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Microfilm 453, 1959-1961 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Microfilm Roll 456, 1959-1963 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Microfilm Roll 457, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Microfilm Roll 458, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Microfilm Roll 461, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Microfilm Roll 463, 1961-1964 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Microfilm Roll 464, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Microfilm Roll 465, 1961-1962 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Microfilm Roll 466, 1961-1963 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Microfilm Roll 469, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Microfilm Roll 473, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Microfilm Roll 475, 1960-1962 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Microfilm Roll 476, 1959-1964 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Microfilm Roll 478, 1955-1958 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Microfilm Roll 483, 1958-1961 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Microfilm Roll 484, 1959-1968 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Microfilm Roll 485, 1959-1961 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Microfilm Roll 488, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Microfilm Roll 489, 1961-1964 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Microfilm Roll 490, 1958-1964 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Microfilm Roll 491, 1962-1965 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Microfilm Roll 492, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Microfilm Roll 493, 1959-1963 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Microfilm Roll 495, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Microfilm Roll 498, 1959-1963 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Microfilm Roll 503, 1960-1964 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Microfilm Roll 504, 1962-1965 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Microfilm Roll 508, 1951-1959 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Microfilm Roll 509, 1959-1963 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Microfilm Roll 511, 1959-1961 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Microfilm Roll 512, 1961-1963 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Microfilm Roll 514, 1960-1962 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Microfilm Roll 515, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Microfilm Roll 517, 1958-1965 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Microfilm Roll 519, 1959-1964 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Microfilm Roll 522, 1961-1964 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Microfilm Roll 523, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Microfilm Roll 524, 1957-1965 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Microfilm Roll 524, 1957-1965 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Microfilm Roll 527, 1961-1962 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Microfilm Roll 536, 1961-1968 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Microfilm Roll 538, 1958-1964 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Microfilm Roll 539, 1960-1964 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Microfilm Roll 543, 1958-1963 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Microfilm Roll 545, 1963-1965 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Microfilm Roll 547, 1958-1961 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Microfilm Roll 548, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Microfilm Roll 549, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Microfilm Roll 550, 1959-1964 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Microfilm Roll 553, 1959-1961 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Microfilm Roll 560, 1959-1962 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Microfilm Roll 563, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Microfilm Roll 564, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Microfilm Roll 565, 1961-1962 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Microfilm Roll 566, 1959-1961 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Microfilm Roll 566, 1959-1961 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Microfilm Roll 565, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Microfilm Roll 567, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Microfilm Roll 596, 1958-1963 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Microfilm Roll 591, 1961-1962 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Microfilm Roll 590, 1960-1963 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Microfilm Roll 587, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Microfilm Roll 568, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Microfilm Roll 573, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Microfilm Roll 577, 1961-1964 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Microfilm Roll 578, 1961-1964 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Microfilm Roll 581, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Microfilm Roll 582, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Microfilm Roll 583, 1958-1961 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Microfilm Roll 584, 1958-1961 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Microfilm Roll 585, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Microfilm Roll 586, 1963-1965 (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Microfilm Roll 593, 1959-1961 (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Microfilm Roll 594, 1963-1965 (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Microfilm Roll 596, 1959-1961 (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Microfilm Roll 597, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Microfilm Roll 600, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Microfilm Roll 605, 1961-1963 (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Microfilm Roll 606, 1959-1962 (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Microfilm Roll 609, 1960-1965 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Microfilm Roll 610, 1961-1964 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Microfilm Roll 611, 1962-1965 (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Microfilm Roll 612, 1960-1963 (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - Microfilm Roll 613, 1961-1964 (Box 15, Folder 76)
  - Microfilm Roll 615, 1962-1965 (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - Microfilm Roll 616, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - Microfilm Roll 618, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - Microfilm Roll 619, 1956-1963 (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - Microfilm Roll 620, 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - Microfilm Roll 622, 1958-1961 (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - Microfilm Roll 623, 1959-1963 (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - Microfilm Roll 624, 1959-1961 (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - Microfilm Roll 625, 1962-1965 (Box 15, Folder 85)
  - Microfilm Roll 626, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Microfilm Roll 628, 1959-1962 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Microfilm Roll 628, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Microfilm Roll 632, 1959-1961 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Microfilm Roll 634, 1958-1961 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Microfilm Roll 635, 1958-1960 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Microfilm Roll 638, 1957-1961 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Microfilm Roll 640, 1961-1962 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Microfilm Roll 641, 1962-1965 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Microfilm Roll 641, 1960-1963 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Microfilm Roll 641, 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Microfilm Roll 642, 1960-1964 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Microfilm Roll 643, 1961-1965 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Microfilm Roll 644, 1959-1962 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Microfilm Roll 652, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Microfilm Roll 657, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Microfilm Roll 658, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Microfilm Roll 663, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Microfilm Roll 665, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Microfilm Roll 666, 1959-1962 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Microfilm Roll 667, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Microfilm Roll 668, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Microfilm Roll 669, 1955-1958 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Microfilm Roll 672, 1955-1964 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Microfilm Roll 674, 1956-1961 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Microfilm Roll 675, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Microfilm Roll 677, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Microfilm Roll 678, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Microfilm Roll 679, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Microfilm Roll 680, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Microfilm Roll 684, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Microfilm Roll 685, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Microfilm Roll 687, 1954 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Microfilm Roll 688, 1953-1956 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Microfilm Roll 693, 1955-1956 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Microfilm Roll 694, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Microfilm Roll 698, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Microfilm Roll 699, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Microfilm Roll 701, 1958-1963 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Microfilm Roll 702, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Microfilm Roll 706 - 707, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Microfilm Roll 708 - 713, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Microfilm Roll 714 - 715, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Microfilm Roll 716 - 718, 1956-1960 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Microfilm Roll 719-725, 1961-1963 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Microfilm Roll 726, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Microfilm Roll 727 - 738, 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Microfilm Roll 739 - 749, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Microfilm Roll 751 - 759, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Microfilm Roll 762 - 769, 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Microfilm Roll 770 - 785, 1964-1968 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Microfilm Roll 786 - 792, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Microfilm Roll 793, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Microfilm Roll 794, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Microfilm Roll 794, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Microfilm Roll 795 - 796, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Microfilm Roll 797 - 798, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Microfilm Roll 799, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Microfilm Roll 800 - 805, 1965-1966 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Microfilm Roll 806 - 807, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Microfilm 808 - 813, 1965-1967 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Microfilm Roll 206, 1955-1957 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Microfilm Roll 207, 1956-1959 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Microfilm Roll 208, 1956-1959 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Microfilm Roll 209, 1955-1958 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Microfilm Roll 210, 1958-1959 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Microfilm Roll 211, 1956-1959 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Microfilm Roll 227, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Microfilm Roll 232, 1953-1955 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Microfilm Roll 233, 1956-1958 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Microfilm Roll 234, 1954-1959 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Microfilm Roll 251, 1956-1958 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Microfilm Roll 258, 1957-1959 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Microfilm Roll 268, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Microfilm Roll 269, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Microfilm Roll 270, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Microfilm Roll 271, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Microfilm Roll 272, 1963-1965 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Microfilm Roll 273, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Microfilm Roll 274, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Microfilm Roll 275, 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Microfilm Roll 276, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Microfilm Roll 277, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Microfilm Roll 278, 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Microfilm Roll 279, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Microfilm Roll 281, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Microfilm Roll 282, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Microfilm Roll 283, 1965-1968 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Microfilm Roll 286, 1962-1965 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Microfilm Roll 287, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Microfilm Roll 288, 1966 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Microfilm Roll 289, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Microfilm Roll 290, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Microfilm Roll 291, 1962-1964 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Microfilm Roll 292, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Microfilm Roll 293, 1963-1965 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Microfilm Roll 294, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Microfilm Roll 295, 1965-1968 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Microfilm Roll 296, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Microfilm Roll 297, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Microfilm Roll 298, 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Microfilm Roll 299, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Microfilm Roll 300, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Microfilm Roll 301, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Microfilm Roll 302, 1964-1965 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Microfilm Roll 303, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Microfilm Roll 304, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Microfilm Roll 305, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Microfilm Roll 306, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Microfilm Roll 308, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Microfilm Roll 307, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Microfilm Roll 309, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Microfilm Roll 310, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Microfilm Roll 311, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Microfilm Roll 311, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Microfilm Roll 312, 1954-1961 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Microfilm Roll 313, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Microfilm Roll 314, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Microfilm Roll 322, 1960-1962 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Microfilm Roll 324, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Microfilm Roll 323, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Microfilm Roll 325, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Microfilm Roll 326, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Microfilm Roll 327, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Microfilm Roll 328, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Microfilm Roll 329, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Microfilm Roll 330, 1962-1963 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - Microfilm Roll 331, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Microfilm Roll 332, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Microfilm Roll 333, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Microfilm Roll 334, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - Microfilm Roll 335, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - Microfilm Roll 336, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - Microfilm Roll 338, 1943-1963 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - Microfilm Roll 339, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Microfilm Roll 340, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - Microfilm Roll 341, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - Microfilm Roll 342, 1957-1963 (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - Microfilm Roll 343, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - Microfilm Roll 345, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - Microfilm Roll 344, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - Microfilm Roll 346, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - Microfilm Roll 1940-1947, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Microfilm Roll 1948, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Microfilm Roll 1949, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Microfilm Roll 1950 - 1952, 1969-1971 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Microfilm Roll 1953 - 1954, 1967-1969 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Microfilm Roll 1955-1957, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Microfilm Roll 1958 - 1961, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Microfilm Roll 1963, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Microfilm Roll 1964, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Microfilm Roll 1964, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Microfilm Roll 1965 - 1967, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Microfilm Roll 1968 - 1972, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Microfilm Roll 1973-1974, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Microfilm Roll 1975 - 1979, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Microfilm Roll 1932, 1967-1973 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Microfilm Roll 1983 - 2002, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Microfilm Roll 2023, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Microfilm Roll 2098 - 2099, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Microfilm Roll 2100, 1971-1975 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Microfilm Roll 2101 - 2103, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Microfilm Roll 2104, 1972-1975 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Microfilm Roll 2105, 1972-1975 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Microfilm Roll 2106, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Microfilm Roll 2107, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Microfilm Roll 2108, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Microfilm Roll 2109, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Microfilm Roll 2110, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Microfilm Roll 2111, 1972-1975 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Microfilm Roll 2112, 1972-1975 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Microfilm Roll 2113, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Microfilm Roll 2114, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Microfilm Roll 2115, 1973-1976 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Microfilm Roll 2116, 1970-1974 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Microfilm Roll 2117, 1969-1975 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Microfilm Roll 2118, 1972-1975 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Microfilm Roll 2119, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Microfilm Roll 2121, 1972-1975 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Microfilm Roll 2122, 1971-1974 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Microfilm Roll 2125, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Microfilm Roll 2127, 1971-1974 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Microfilm Roll 814 - 816, 1964-1968 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Microfilm Roll 817 - 819, 1964-1968 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Microfilm Roll 820 - 829, 1964-1968 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Microfilm Roll 830 - 842, 1963-1966 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Microfilm Roll 843 - 847, 1964-1968 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Microfilm Roll 848 - 853, 1964-1968 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Microfilm Roll 854 - 859, 1965-1968 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Microfilm Roll 860 - 869, 1963-1967 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Microfilm Roll 890 - 899, 1961-1967 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Microfilm Roll 880 - 889, 1964-1967 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Microfilm Roll 871 - 879, 1965-1968 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Microfilm Roll 900 - 904, 1965-1968 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Microfilm Roll 905, 1963-1968 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Microfilm Roll 906 - 912, 1963-1968 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Microfilm Roll 913 - 919, 1961-1968 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Microfilm Roll 920 - 922, 1964-1967 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Microfilm Roll 923, 1962-1967 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Microfilm Roll 924 - 925, 1959-1968 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Microfilm Roll 926 - 927, 1963-1968 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Microfilm Roll 929 - 931, 1964-1967 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Microfilm Roll 945 - 947, 1964-1968 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Microfilm Roll 932 - 943, 1963-1968 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Microfilm Roll 948 - 949, 1963-1966 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Microfilm Roll 950, 1964-1967 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Microfilm Roll 951 - 954, 1964-1968 (Box 19, Folder 25)